

 $\times$ 

peterhoxuandung@outlook.com

+84 943 417821



Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam



peterho249.github.io

#### in

linkedin.com/in/peterhoxuandun



+84943417821



github.com/PeterHo249

## **SKILLS**

Flutter

Swift 4

Firebase

**JavaScript** 

NodeJS

HTML

CSS

MongoDB

MySQL





## INTERESTS

Reading books

Listening to music

Traveling

# Dung Xuan Ho

## Mobile Developer

Highly responsibility, willingness to learn new things, independent working and positive teamwork attitudes. With the knowledge and skills which I learnt in university and the experience of Flutter, Swift, I want to become part of your mobile development team to create products together.

## **EDUCATION**

## **Bachelor of Software Engineering** HCMVNU - University of Science

09/2015 – 05/2019 GPA: 7.96

## **EXPERIENCE**

## Fast Store - Freelance project (04/2019 - 05/2019)

- Built front-end for department store.
- Using Firebase to push notification.
- Tech stack: Flutter, Firebase Cloud Function and Cloud Messaging.

#### Success Hunter - Thesis project (09/2018 – 04/2019)

- Developed an application to support self development process using Gamification method.
- Tech stack: Flutter, Firebase service (Firestore, Cloud Function, Cloud Messaging, Cloud Pub/sub).
- Apple App Store: itunes.apple.com/us/app/success-hunter/id1451431732?mt=8.
- Google Play Store: play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.hoxuandung.successhunter.

## Kanbanize - Course project (04/2018 – 07/2018)

- Developed an application to manage todo list with Kanban method on iOS.
- Tech stack: Swift 4, Core Data.
- Repository: github.com/PeterHo249/KANBANize.

## Rex Shop - Course project (04/2018 - 07/2018)

- Built a camera and accessory shop website.
- Tech stack: Expressjs with HandlebarsJS, MongoDB.
- Repository: github.com/PeterHo249/rexshop.

#### Yame Shop - Course Project (04/2018 – 07/2018)

- Developed a cloth shop website with pure NodeJS and xml file.
- Tech stack: NodeJS, xml data file.
- Repository: github.com/PeterHo249/yameshop.

## Quick Note - Course Project (12/2017 – 01/2018)

- Developed a note tool for Windows, using hotkey to add note. It's written in C/C++ and Win32 API.
- □ Tech stack: C/C++, Win32 API.
- Repository: github.com/PeterHo249/quicknote.

## Five in a Row game - Course Project (12/2016 – 01/2017)

- Developed five in a row game can be play on console screen. It provide 2 play mode: person-vs-person and person-vs-computer.
- Tech stack: C/C++.
- Repository: github.com/PeterHo249/five in a row